<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/">

<channel>
    <title>Studio CiTA Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.cita.hr/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Studio CiTA is an experienced engineering studio that specializes in developing challenging websites and performing online stores.</description>
    <language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.cita.hr/en/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    <sy:updatePeriod>daily</sy:updatePeriod>
    <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency><item>
        <title>So you think your website is doing great</title>
        <link>https://www.cita.hr/en/blog/website-101/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Silvestar Bistrović]]></dc:creator>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cita.hr/en/blog/website-101/</guid>

        <description><![CDATA[Most websites are not perfect, far from it. There are so many things that could go wrong or just be forgotten.]]></description>

        <content:encoded><![CDATA[
            <h1>So you think your website is doing great</h1>
<p>Most websites are not perfect, far from it. There are so many things that could go wrong or just be forgotten.</p>
<p>If you're not a web professional, you might not care. What you don't know cannot hurt you, right? Of course, that is not the correct way of thinking. Instead, you should hire a professional web developer who can help elevate your online presence and help you grow and expand your business.</p>
<p>You website presence is all about technical correctness and traffic. While traffic cannot be controlled, technical details can be improved and optimized.</p>
<p>Let's says your website have HTML errors. While browsers can be forgiving and display the website (almost) correctly, other tools can penalise you. Sometimes even valid but poorly structured HTML code can hurt your scores. For example, Google might struggle to crawl your site if there are errors too severe or if your site does not use semantic tags.</p>
<p>Broken JavaScript won't hurt only your scores, but it will stop your site from working correctly. Too much JavaScript might slow your site and you will be penalised because your PageSpeed scores will be too low.</p>
<p>Bloated CSS might slow rendering of your site which might case layout shifts and styling bugs that are hard to debug and fix.</p>
<p>You might not know how to add og images or structured data and you might miss some nice search page result features.</p>
<p>Don't get us started about website security that most people take for granted these days. Websites get hacked daily.</p>
<p>So. Many. Things.</p>
<p>So many things that you might never heard of but can help you establish a better presence for you and your business online. Better presence than your competitors. Better presence that will attract more visitors. Better presence which will generate more leads. Better presence that will increase your revenue.</p>
<p>Find yourself a reliable web developer that will handle all of these things for you.</p>
<p>Keep an eye on this blog as we plan to write more about developing a success website from our own human experience.</p>

        ]]></content:encoded>
    </item></channel>
</rss>
